Raksha Nayak

Bengaluru, 560037 | +91 9527550874 | rakshaprema123@gmail.com | www.linkedin.com/in/raksha-nayak125

Summary

Proficient Quality Analyst with 3.5 years of experience handling and resolving critical quality problems using research abilities. Strong analytical, organizational and planning abilities. Consistently works with minimum supervision. Independent and self-directed. Have a good functional experience in Healthcare Domain.

Skills

- Cross-Functional Team Collaboration
- Defect Tracking and Reporting
- Manual Testing
- JIRA
- TOSCA
- MySQL Workbench

- Functional Testing
- Regression Testing
- Test Automation
- X-Ray
- Agile Methodologies
- Salesforce Health Cloud

Experience

Application Development Associate, 01/2021-12/2022 – Accenture, Bengaluru, India Application Development Analyst, 01/2023 – Current, Accenture, Bengaluru, India

Project – Novartis LEAP (03/2021 – Present) Role – Salesforce Tester

- Hands on experience with Health Cloud and Salesforce Admin.
- Developed and maintained test plans, cases, scripts, and data for manual and automated testing.
- Conducted manual and automation testing for Salesforce web applications, including functional, regression and user acceptance testing.
- Identified, documented, and tracked software defects using bug tracking tools such as JIRA, ensuring timely resolution.
- Tested functionality, performance and compliance of each product against design specifications to maintain strong development standards and high customer satisfaction.
- Learned and contributed to the development of automated test scripts using TOSCA.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams including developers, business analysts, and product managers to ensure product quality and alignment with requirements.
- Communicated effectively both verbally and written with internal stakeholders at all levels.
- Worked with Agile and Scrum methodologies to accomplish project milestones and meet demanding timelines.
- Participated in Agile ceremonies such as sprint planning, daily stand-ups, and retrospectives to ensure efficient project delivery.
- Lead a team of 3 junior testers.

Education

Sr. No	Education	Name of Institution	Year of Passing	Name of Board/University	Percentage
1	Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering	Goa College of Engineering	2020	Goa University	72.52%
2	Higher Secondary School Certificate	Don Bosco Higher Secondary School	2016	Goa Board	82.5%
3	Secondary School Certificate	People's High School	2014	Goa Board	86.5%

Additional Technical Skills

- Salesforce Admin
- C++
- Java
- Data Structures using Java
- HTML, CSS & JavaScript

Certifications

- Salesforce Certified Administrator
- Tricentis Tosca Fundamentals Automating Web application testing (AS1)

Accomplishments

• Extra Mile Award for successfully delivering exceptional outcomes with speed and agility by collaborating with clients

Personal Details

- Date of Birth 14th October 1998
- Nationality Indian
- Marital Status Single
- Hobbies Reading, Music
- Languages Known English, Hindi, Konkani, Kannada